Found an existing package already installed. Trying to upgrade the installed package...
Found Git [Git.Git] Version 2.55.0.3
This application is licensed to you by its owner.
Microsoft is not responsible for, nor does it grant any licenses to, third-party packages.
Downloading https://github.com/git-for-windows/git/releases/download/v2.55.0.windows.3/Git-2.55.0.3-64-bit.exe
Successfully verified installer hash
Starting package install...
The installer will request to run as administrator. Expect a prompt.
Successfully installed
